Guide to the Vassar College Facilities Operations Records, 1800s-2021 (bulk 1908-1999)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Administrative Files, 1879-2011
  - Lisburne Grange - Water Supply, 1946-1950 (Box 8)
  - Lisburne Grange, 1946-1952 (Box 8)
  - Vassar College Property Records, 1940-1946 (Box 8)
  - V. C. Property - Beadle House Nantucket (sold 1938), 1934-1937 (Box 8)
  - [Faculty Housing] Specification for Faculty Housing for Vassar College, 1965 (Box 8)
  - [Williams House] Williams Hall - Specifications, undated (Box 8)
  - [Faculty Housing] 114 Raymond Avenue - Wood House, General Specifications Alterations, Miss Washburn, 1917; (3 folders) (Box 8)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Development Proposed, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
  - [Kendrick House] [Kendrick House Construction], 1926-1928; (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Letter to Highway Committee Chairman Edward Schofield, 1941; (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - [Kendrick House] Campbell, George D., Inc., 1928 (Box 8)
  - [Kendrick House] Collins - Wagner Mfg. Co., 1927 (Box 8)
  - [Kendrick House] Costs, 1926-1929 (Box 8)
  - [Kendrick House] Furnishings, 1927 (Box 8)
  - [Kendrick House] General, 1926-1928 (Box 8)
  - [Kendrick House] [Kendrick Hall Stonework], 1926 (Box 8)
  - [Library - Thompson] [Specifications for Thompson Memorial Library], undated (Box 8)
  - [Library - Thompson] [Library Addition Shelving], 1917 (Box 8)
  - [Library - Thompson] [Library Tower Roofing], 1933 (Box 8)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Lighting, 1951-1953 (Box 8)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall (and Van Ingen) Conversion from DC to AC, 1955 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] [Specification For The General Construction Addition To The Library and West Wing, Vassar College], 1936 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] [Vassar College Library Plumbing], 1936 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Furnishings, 1936-1937 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Allen, Collens and Willis, 1935-1937; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Extras, 1936-1938 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Edgar V. Anderson, 1936-1937; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Costs - Certificates, 1935-1937 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Budget, 1936-1938 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen Equipment, 1934-1937 (Box 9)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen General, 1935-1937 (Box 9)
  - [Main Building] [Main Building Alteration, Wainscotting Dining Room and Stair Towers], 1918-1931 (Box 9)
  - [New England Building] Glass Laboratory, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
  - [Metcalf House] Metcalf House, 1915 (Box 9)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] Power House, 1933-1936 (Box 9)
  - [Wimpfheimer Nursery School] Anderson, Edgar V., 1926-1927 (Box 9)
  - [Wimpfheimer Nursery School] Equipment, 1927-1928 (Box 9)
  - [Wimpfheimer Nursery School] General, 1926-1928 (Box 9)
  - [Wimpfheimer Nursery School] [Specifications for Nursery School at Vassar College], 1926 (Box 9)
  - [Main Building] Structural Repairs, 1955-1963 (Box 9)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Student Room Alterations, 1959-1963; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - [Faculty Housing] MacCracken House Roof and Renovations, 1925 (Box 9)
  - [Raymond House] Raymond Hall Specifications, 1925 (Box 9)
  - [Rockefeller Hall] [Specification for Heating - Rockefeller Hall], undated (Box 9)
  - [Williams House] Williams Hall - Heating, 1924-1925 (Box 9)
  - [Sanders Physics] Physics Laboratory for Vassar College, 1924 (Box 10)
  - [Sanders Physics] Specifications for Plumbing Work for the Physics Laboratory Building, 1925 (Box 10)
  - [Sanders Physics] Physics Laboratory Specifications Revised October 1924, Addenda December 1924 (Box 10)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry Lab, 1908-1926 (Box 10)
  - [Sanders Physics] Sanders Physics Laboratory for Vassar College, Outline Specifications, 1922 (Box 10)
  - Josselyn Hall, 1911; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - [General Manager] Report of the General Manager and Consulting Engineer to the President and the board of Trustees, Vassar College, 1950; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - [Jewett House] Jewett House Bake Oven, 1940 (Box 10)
  - Greenhouse Lord and Burnham, 1937-1938 (Box 10)
  - Garage, 1930-1931 (Box 10)
  - Specifications for New Garage at Vassar, 1930-1931 (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Sports Building Specifications for Heating and Ventilation Systems Office Copy, 1933; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Specifications for Construction of The Sports Building, Vassar College, 1930-1933 (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Specifications for Electrical System for the Gymnasium Building, Vassar College, 1933 (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Furnishings and Regulation, 1932-1935; (4 folders) (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Sports Building Construction and Photographic Negatives, 1930-1932 (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Construction, 1933-1934 (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall - Correspondence and Orders from Allen and Collens, 1930-1933; (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Construction Specifications, 1928-1932 (Box 11)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Vassar Sports Building - Heating. Plumbing and Electric, 1928-1934 (Box 11)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Flooring, Pool and Bleachers, 1928-1933 (Box 11)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Construction Specifications, 1928-1932; (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Electrical, Heating and Ventilating, 1933-1934 (Box 11)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Hall Plumbing Specification, 1930 (Box 11)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Edgar V. Anderson, Roofing Bond and Guarantee, 1933 (Box 11)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Schedule of Hardware from Chandler and Barber Co. for Sports Building, 1933 (Box 11)
  - Claim of Damages, Bill of Particulars Exhibits A, B, C and D - Supplementary Data Sheet Forwarded to Mr. Robert B. Van De Water, 1967 (Box 11)
  - [Student Housing] [H-V-D Loan Copy Application Residence Dormitories (Stubbins) House 1 for 294], 1970 (Box 11)
  - [Student Housing] [Vassar College Residences Specifications (Official Marked Up Copy of Addendums], 1970 (Box 11)
  - Construction Ledger, 1925-1950 (Box 11)
  - Easements - N. Y. State Dept. of Public Works Raymond Avenue Reconstruction, 1961-1965 (Box 11)
  - [Alumnae House] Vassar College Insurance Tax Records - Alumnae House, 1961-1969 (Box 11)
  - Raymond Avenue Reconstruction Special Claims For Damages, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Raymond Avenue Reconstruction for Claims of Damages Filed With N. Y. State Court of Claims, 1963-1969 (Box 11)
  - Raymond Avenue Reconstruction - V. C. Claims for Damages, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Easements - N. Y. State Dept. of Public Works Raymond Avenue Reconstruction, 1961-1970; (4 folders) (Box 11)
  - Photographs - Raymond Avenue Reconstruction East Side Raymond Avenue (Photographs, Henry Reichert), 1965 (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Raymond Avenue Reconstruction West Side Raymond Avenue (Photographs, Henry Reichert), 1965 (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Raymond Ave. - 4 Extra Views Taylor Hall and Chapel, South of Kendricks Hall Looking West, North of Kendricks Hall and Parking Lot Looking East South of College View Ave. - 4 Negatives Enclosed (Henry Reichert, Photographer), 1965 (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Chapel Walk, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Raymond and Hooker Ave. - Enclosed Black and White Photos and Negatives Starting From Vassar Lake Drive Looking North #1, Then South to Hooker Ave. Back North to Skinner Hall #23, 1965; (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Raymond Avenue Reconstruction - Progress Photographs - Views of Raymond and Hooker Avenues, 1965; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Raymond Avenue Reconstruction - Progress Photographs, Raymond and Hooker Avenues, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Dining Facility, Hugh Stubbins and Associates, 1969 (Box 12)
  - [Student Housing] Stubbins Dormitory (Not Done) Reports On Expenditures, undated (Box 12)
  - [Student Housing] Dining Facility Hugh Stubbins and Associates, Inc Architect, 1969 (Box 12)
  - [Student Housing] General, Hugh Stubbins and Associates, 1969-1971 (Box 12)
  - [Student Housing] Distribution of Plans and Specifications, Hugh Stubbins and Associates, 1971 (Box 12)
  - [Student Housing] Specifications, Hugh Stubbins and Associates, 1970 (Box 12)
  - [Student Housing] Invitation to Bid, Hugh Stubbins and Associates, 1971 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Steam Plant Modernization Payments to Burns and Roe, Inc, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Power Dept. - Ash Handling System, 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - [Alumnae House] Alumnae House Alterations - By Campbell Building Co., 1957-1958 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler House Auxiliaries, 1961 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Steam Plant Modernization Materials Sent to Burns and Roe, 1961 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Power Dept. - Erection of Mechanical Equipment and Piping, 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Power Dept. Coal Crusher, 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler House Etc., 1949 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Unit No. 5 - Circulating System for Condenser - Estimates, 1932; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler House Sketches, 1932 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler House Sketches - Heat, undated (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Radiation and Mains- College Ave. Houses, 1927-1928 (Box 12)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] [Power House Sketches], 1932 Apr, 1936 Feb (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Unit No. 2 Water Rate Tests (Engine Room Readings), Dec. 8, 1936-1937 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Unit No. 5 Water Rate Tests (Engine Room Readings) Tests No. 1 and 2, 1932 Oct 18 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] [Heat], 1932 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Power Dept. - Ash Handling System Construction L. Yanko, Inc., 1960 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Power Dept. - Ash Handling System, 1960 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Power Dept. - Deaerating Feedwater Heater, 1960 (Box 12)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Power Dept. - Ash Handling System Coal Firing Test Report, 1961 (Box 12)
  - [Baldwin Hall] Baldwin House Alterations Material Sent To Architects, 1961 (Box 12)
  - [Faculty Housing] Inspection Reports, 1961 (Box 12)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Ackerman, Know, Hayward and Pakan, Engineers, 1961-1964; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Carl Koch Architect, 1961-1964 (Box 12)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Clarke and Rapuano Landscape Architects, 1960-1967 (Box 12)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Davies Brothers Corp. Contractor, 1965-1967 (Box 12)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Project - Lien Waivers, 1965-1967 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Specifications (Rough Draft), 1965 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Specifications Landscaping - Vassar College Faculty Housing, Poughkeepsie, New York, 1966 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing - Triangle Area Ackerman, Knox, Hayward and Pakan, 1965 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Proposal, Contract and Specifications for Water Mains, Services and Appurtenances, 1960 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites, 1961-1963 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Triangle Area, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Construction, 1965 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Specifications for Faculty Housing For Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, New York, 1970 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Sites - Construction, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Project Change Order, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Project Landscaping Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 13)
  - [Faculty Housing] Photographs Showing Various Sections Of The Collapsed Platform Roof Which Occurred On The Afternoon Of June 3 1966 - Davies Brothers Corp. (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Addition, 1960-1962 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Addition General, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Addition (Proposed), 1956-1959 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Conference Reports By Mr. Hutchins, 1960 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Addition Payments to Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott, Architects, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Addition Taylor Alterations Material Sent To Architects, 1959-1964; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Invitations To Bid, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Contract Award, 1961 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Change Orders - Library, 1961-1964 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library - Construction, 1962-1965 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Construction, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Addition Furniture, 1960-1964 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations Sculpture Gallery, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations General, 1963-1965; (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] [Library Addition - Payments to Geo. A Fuller Co. Contractor], 1961-1964 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations Payments to Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott, Architects, 1960-1963 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations Payments To Contractor, 1961-1963 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations General, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations, 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations Large Lecture Hall, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Invitations To Bid, 1961 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations Specifications, 1961 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Construction, 1961 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Change Orders, 1961-1964 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Contract Award Phase II, 1961 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Construction, 1961-1964 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations Furniture, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alterations Sculpture Court, 1962-1963; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Centennial Celebration (General), 1961 (Box 14)
  - Command Performance, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1959-1961; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Contemporary Arts Conference, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Academic Convocation, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Centennial Mid-Nineteenth Century Festival, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Alumnae Day, 1959-1961 (Box 14)
  - Centennial Celebration Art Exhibition, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Boots and Saddle Horseshow, 1960 (Box 14)
  - International Conference, 1959-1961 (Box 14)
  - Centennial Celebration - Minutes, 1961 (Box 14)
  - Centennial Celebration - Reports to Trustees, 1959-1960 (Box 14)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations Payments to Goldstone and Dearborn, 1958-1961 (Box 14)
  - [Main Building] [Main Building Alterations - Payments To Campbell Building Company], 1959-1961 (Box 14)
  - [Main Building] Progress Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations Progress Photographs, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations General, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] [Alterations To Main Building, Vassar College Specifications], 1959-1960 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alteration Program Goldstone and Dearborn Material Sent To The Architects, 1957-1960 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alteration Program, 1957-1958 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations, 1958-1959 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations Specifications, 1959-1960; (3 folders) (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Proposed Administration Building Receipts For Material Sent To Architect And Engineers, 1957 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Invitations To Bid, 1959 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations Conference Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Change Orders, 1960-1961; (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Contract Award, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Contract Award Elevator, 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Construction, 1959-1961 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Proposed Administration Building General, 1954 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Proposed Administration Building and Alterations to Reports By Eero Saarinen, 1954-1955 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Structural Repairs, 1959-1962; (6 folders) (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Furniture and Equipment, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations Landscaping, 1961; (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - [Main Building] Cooperative Bookshop, 1960 (Box 16)
  - [Main Building] First Floor - Transverse, 1960 (Box 16)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Alterations - 1st Fl. South Transverse Payments To Campbell Building Co., 1960 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility, 1981 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House Survey - Muzak Of The Mid-Hudson Valley, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Proposed Athletic Facilities, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Contract, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Change Estimates, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House - Alarm System, 1982-1985; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker - Audio Visual System, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Evaluation of Sound System Submittals For Walker Field House, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Bleachers, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Fuel and Electric Costs For Walker Field House, 1982 Nov (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Carpet, undated (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Concrete Test Reports, 1981 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Electrical, 1981-1984 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Oildraulic Elevator Contract Data, 1981 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Equipment and Furnishings, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Finish Hardware, 1981 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility - Floor Covering, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility - Graphics, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility HVAC and Shop Drawings, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Kitchen Equipment, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Landscaping, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Lockers, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Painting, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Plumbing, 1983-1984; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House Interior and Exterior Photographs, Wayne Soverns, Jr., 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Photos, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Plumbing Shop Drawings, 1983 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Roofing, 1981-1984 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Schedule, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Seating, 1982 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility - Security, 1983 (Box 16)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House - Sound System, 1982 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Sprinklers, 1981-1983 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House - Squash Courts, 1984 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House - Storm Drainage, 1983 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Subcontractors, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Specifications (Extras - Incomplete), 1981 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facilities Shop Drawing, 1981 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facilities Sprinkler Shop Drawings, 1982 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Swimming Pool, 1981-1984 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Telephones, 1982 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Physical Education Building, 1981-1984 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility - Job meeting Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Change Orders, 1981-1983 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Payments To Architect, 1981 (Box 17)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Building - Letters Of Transmittal and Various Correspondence, 1981 (Box 17)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Installation Of Additional Steam Boiler [Payments To Burns and Roe, Inc., Invitations To Bid, Contract Award, Specifications and Plans.], 1962-1964 (Box 17)
  - [Utilities] Improvements To Fire Protection System and Payments, 1962-1963 (Box 17)
  - Letters Of Requisition - Mylar Signs, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Laundry Building Conversion, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - [Chapel] Chapel Alterations Construction, 1966-1968 (Box 17)
  - [Chapel] Chapel Alterations [Change Orders], 1966-1967; (6 folders) (Box 17)
  - [Student Housing] Partial Consolidation Food Service Facilities General, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - [Student Housing] Partial Consolidation Dining Facilities General, 1966 (Box 18)
  - [Student Housing] Consolidated Dining Facilities Goldstone and Dearborn Architect, 1965-1969 (Box 18)
  - [Chapel] Chapel Organ, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
  - [Chapel] Chapel Alterations E.W. Howell Co. Contractor, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - [Chapel] Chapel Alterations General, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
  - [Chapel] Chapel Alterations Architect, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
  - [Chapel] Chapel Alterations - Specifications (Electrical, Plumbing, Heating and Ventilating), 1966 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Laundry Building Conversion Invitations To Bid, 1966 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Laundry Building Conversion Specifications, 1966 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Laundry Building Conversion, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Laundry Building Conversion Construction, 1966-1968 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Laundry Building Construction Change Orders, 1966 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Computer Center Contractor, 1966-1967 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Computer Center Goldstone and Dearborn Architect, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Kuhn, Smith and Harris, Inc - Bid proposal, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - [Student Housing] Dining Facilities #7 Model Photographs Quadrangle Project In Detail Josselyn-Jewett Project In Preliminary Form, 1967; (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - [Student Housing] Partial Consolidation Food Service Facilities General, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
  - [Student Housing] Invitations To Bid, 1966 (Box 18)
  - [Student Housing] Quadrangle Alterations and Dining Building Specifications, 1967 (Box 18)
  - [Student Housing] Consolidated Dining Facilities Change Orders, 1966 (Box 18)
  - [Noyes House] Proposed Dormitory Contract Award, 1957 (Box 18)
  - [Noyes House] Noyes House Executed Contract Documents, 1957; (4 folders) (Box 18)
  - [Noyes House] Construction, 1958-1959 (Box 18)
  - [Noyes House] Saarinen Dormitory - Statements Saarinen - Architect Post - Food Service Consultant, 1955-1958 (Box 18)
  - [Noyes House] Executed Contract Documents, 1958 (Box 18)
  - [Noyes House] Vassar College and The Chase Manhattan Bank - Indenture of Mortgage and Trust Dated as of April 1, 1957 (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] Subcontractors, 1957 (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] Proposed Dormitory Receipts For Material Sent To Architect and Engineer, 1955-1958 (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] Construction HHFA Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] Proposed Dormitory (Saarinen), 1955-1959; (3 folders) (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] Proposed Dormitory (Saarinen) Photographs Of Model, 1959 (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] [Vassar College Contract Documents - New Dormitory Project No. NY 30-CH-43 (D) (Office Copy)], 1957 (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] Noyes house Furnishings - Statements Eero Saarinen and Associates, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
  - [Noyes House] Quarterly Reports Status of Construction, 1957-1959 (Box 19)